Muhannad Salkini

Software Developer

Experience

• Back-end Developer Intern, 02/2024 - 05/2024 (4 months) · Elmali Tech – Istanbul, Turkey

Interned at Elmali Tech, honing back-end development skills in Node.js and TypeScript. Contributed to serverside logic, API development, and database management in a dynamic tech environment

Information Technology Intern, 07/2023 - 09/2023
 (2 months) · Karabuk University – Karabuk, Turkey

Interned at Directorate of Information Technology, handling network, technical support, camera operations, and support services.

E-commerce, 10/2018 - 05/2022
 (3 years 7 months) · Self-employed – Turkey

Successfully managed my own e-commerce venture in Turkey, specializing in selling 3D printers and related components.

Education

• Turkey, Karabuk University
Bachelor of Computer Engineering · (2019 - 2024)

Course & Certifications

- Oracle Database Design & Programming Certificates
- Almdrasa Git and GitHub Certificate
- Stanford Uni. Supervised ML Regression and Classification
- TÜBİTAK Science Fair Participation Certificates
- AFAD Disaster Awareness Education Programs

Languages

- Turkish Native
- Arabic Native
- English Professional

Contact

mohanad.salkini@gmail.com +90 (536) 240 62 03

LinkedIn:

<u>linkedin.com/in/muhannad-salkini</u>

GitHup:

github.com/muhannadsalkini

Website:

muhannad.salkini.me

Summary

I'm Muhannad, a dedicated Web developer driven by a profound passion for software craftsmanship. I've honed my skills with MERN stack, Laravel, and advanced database designs. I've also crafted APIs in C# and built different systems using ASP.net showcasing my adaptability and project management abilities.

Currently, immersed in MERN stack projects, leveraging NodeJS and MongoDB for backend and React with Tailwind CSS for frontend development.

I bring leadership experience from contributing to managing several clubs like Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC) and a commitment to excellence.

Relevant Skills

Programming Languages and Frameworks:

- JavaScript Frameworks: Node.js, ReactJS (including experience with Express.js, typescript)
- PHP Frameworks: LaravelC# Frameworks: .NET

Web Development:

- REST API Development
- Backend Development: Typescript, JavaScript, PHP
- Frontend Development: HTML5, CSS (Tailwind)
- Database Management: MongoDB, MySQL, MS SQL, Oracle
- Version Control: Git/GitHub
- Operating Systems: Windows and Linux

Personal Skills

Teamwork Self-Learning
Time Management Research
Creativity Planning

Riccialization Research

Discipline Problem Solving